Guide to the International Federation of Professional and Technical Engineers, Local 66 Records WAG.010
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series II: Records of the International Union, 1936-1978, 2
  - Councils and Committees of the International: Legislative conference memos and texts, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Councils and Committees of the International: Outlook office reports, correspondence about articles, 1950-1962 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Councils and Committees of the International: Outlook office reports, correspondence about articles, 1950-1962 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Councils and Committees of the International: Special Committee on Regional vice presidencies, 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Officers and Representatives of the International: Pres. Russell Stephens's trip to ILO conference, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Officers and Representatives of the International: Secy-treas. Ross, 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Officers and Representatives of the International: Secy-treas. Woodside (see also 8/16), 1965 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Officers and Representatives of the International: V.P. Anderson, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Officers and Representatives of the International: V.P. Bower, 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Officers and Representatives of the International: V.P. Timothy Flynn, 1959-1961 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Officers and Representatives of the International: V.P. Nelson, 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Officers and Representatives of the International: V.P. Edmund Noetzel, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Officers and Representatives of the International: V.P. Smook, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Officers and Representatives of the International: V.P. John Young, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Officers and Representatives of the International: International Rep. Francis Forst (see also 6/10), 1965 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Officers and Representatives of the International: International Rep. Miles Holmes, includes arbitrator's award for Local 119. (See also 25/30-1931), 1958-1965 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Officers and Representatives of the International: International Rep. Melrose Kerr, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Officers and Representatives of the International: International Rep. Joseph McCann, with reports, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Officers and Representatives of the International: International Rep. Harold Weissman, 1955-1957 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Officers and Representatives of the International: International Rep. James Woodside, with reports (see also 8/3), 1958-1964 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Officers and Representatives of the International: Organizer John O'Leary, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - International Conventions:(IFTEADU in Denver) includes report of Local 66 delegates delegates' report and amendment vote, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - International Conventions: (AFTE, Philadelphia) delegates report and amendment vote, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - International Conventions: (AFTE), 1956 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - International Conventions: (AFTE) instruction to Local 66 delegates and resolution, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - International Conventions: (AFTE, Seattle) Officers' report to 36th convention, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - International Conventions: (AFTE, St. Louis) Proceedings and addendum, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - International Conventions: (AFTE, Milwaukee) Program book, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - International Conventions: (IFPTE, Chicago) Proceedings and notes for delegates report; officers' report, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - International Conventions: (IFPTE, Chicago) Proceedings and notes for delegates report; officers' report, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - International Conventions: (IFPTE) Officers' report; Local 66 resolutions, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - International Conventions: (IFPTE) Officers' report; Local 66 resolutions, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - International Conventions: (IFPTE, Honolulu) Officers' report to 43rd convention, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - IFTEADU in NLRB and NWLB Arbitrations: (NLRB) Curtiss-Wright vs. UOPWA (IFTEADU as intervenor, to claim engineering bargaining unit), 1945 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - IFTEADU in NLRB and NWLB Arbitrations: (NLRB) Curtiss-Wright vs. UOPWA (IFTEADU as intervenor, to claim engineering bargaining unit), 1945 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - IFTEADU in NLRB and NWLB Arbitrations: (NLRB) Curtiss-Wright vs. UOPWA (IFTEADU as intervenor, to claim engineering bargaining unit), 1945 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - IFTEADU in NLRB and NWLB Arbitrations: (NLRB) Curtiss-Wright vs. UOPWA (IFTEADU as intervenor, to claim engineering bargaining unit), 1945 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - IFTEADU in NLRB and NWLB Arbitrations: (NLRB) Curtiss-Wright vs. UOPWA (IFTEADU as intervenor, to claim engineering bargaining unit), 1945 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - IFTEADU in NLRB and NWLB Arbitrations: (NWLB) Struthers-Well Corp. vs. IFTEADU Locals 52 and 55 (classifications and rates of pay), 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - IFTEADU in NLRB and NWLB Arbitrations: (NWLB) Struthers-Well Corp. vs. IFTEADU Locals 52 and 55 (classifications and rates of pay), 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - IFTEADU in NLRB and NWLB Arbitrations: (NWLB) Lozier, Inc. vs. Local 30 (transcript of JLR's testimony on representation during wartime), 1943 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - IFTEADU in NLRB and NWLB Arbitrations: (NWLB) Bethlehem Steel Co. vs. Local 97: arbitration of wartime contract negotiations, 1943-1945 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - IFTEADU in NLRB and NWLB Arbitrations: (NWLB) Bethlehem Steel Co. vs. Local 97: arbitration of wartime contract negotiations, 1943-1945 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - IFTEADU in NLRB and NWLB Arbitrations: (NWLB) Bethlehem Steel Co. vs. Local 97: arbitration of wartime contract negotiations, 1943-1945 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Publications of the International: (IFTEADU) Souvenir booklet for 25th anniversary, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Publications of the International: (IFTEADU) Monthly Outlook, #61, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Publications of the International: (IFTEADU) Information Letter, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Publications of the International: (IFTEADU) Research and Collective Bargaining Bulletin, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Publications of the International: (AFTE) "Federal Newsletter" of Engineers Outlook, 1953-1965 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Publications of the International: (AFTE) Engineers Outlook, 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Publications of the International: (AFTE) Engineers Outlook, 1963-1970 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Publications of the International: (AFTE) Engineers Outlook, 1963-1970 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Publications of the International: (AFTE) Engineers Outlook, 1971, 75 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Publications of the International: (AFTE) "Labor-management reporting and disclosure act", 1959 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Publications of the International: (AFTE) "For Local Union Research File" #2, #7, 1966, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Publications of the International: (IFPTE) "Manual of Policies, revised", 1978 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Canadian Council, 1962, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Delaware Valley Council (and member locals), 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Northeast Council conference on organizing campaign, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Northeast Council minutes, 1963-1968 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Northeast Council includes notices, notes (by Rymer), 1963-1968 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Northeast Council (and member locals), 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Northeast Council (circulars from Local 66), 1952-1964 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 2 (NYC public sector), 1951-1965 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 3 (Philadelphia), 1937-1951 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 4 (New Hampshire) and newsletter, 1966, 1937-1958, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 4 (New Hampshire) and newsletter, 1966, 1937-1958, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 5 (Rhode Island) and resumes of members, 1937-1949 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 6 (Charleston, SC), 1937-1952 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 7 (Massachusetts), 1937-1958 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 8 (Vallejo, CA), 1937-1956 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 11 (San Francisco), 1937-1952 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 12 (Bremerton, WA), 1937-1960 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 13 (Philadelphia), 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 15 (Boston area), 1937-1952 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 17 (Seattle, WA) and publications from 60s, 1937-1969 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 17 on "threat to disaffiliate", 1969 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 23 (St. Louis), 1941-1958 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 23 (St. Louis), 1941-1958 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 24 (Jamestown, NY) contracts and exhibits, 1943-1945 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 24, 1948-1957 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 27 (Durham, NC), 1942-1944 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 39 (Oakland, CA), 1937-1951 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 46 (Washington, DC), 1937-1954 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 55 (Warren, PA), 1943-1945, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 55 (Warren, PA), 1943-1945, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 63 (Perth Amboy, NJ), 1937-1956 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 66 (letters from JLR to locals he served as VP), 1951 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 76 (Bedford, IN), 1940-1950 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 77 (Bloomington, IN), 1940-1941 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 80 (Jersey City, NJ), 1963 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 89 (Oakland, CA), 1943-1948 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 90-A (Chicago- reaffiliated) - chemical contracts (see also former rival, Local 143), 1963 (Box 9, Folder 24A)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 91 (New Orleans), 1943 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence of the IFTEADU/AFTE/IFPTE Regional Councils and Locals: Local 97 (Stowe, PA), 1965 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Local 101 (Minneapolis), 1950-1953 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Local 105 (Boston) contract, division officers, MTA negotiations, 1945,47-1963 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Local 105 (Boston) contract, division officers, MTA negotiations, 1945,47-1963 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Local 105 (Boston) contract, division officers, MTA negotiations, 1945,47-1963 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Local 105 (Boston) contract, division officers, MTA negotiations, 1945,47-1963 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Local 105 (Boston) contract, division officers, MTA negotiations, 1945,47-1963 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Local 112 (Springfield, MA) includes ARMA arbitration, 1947-1961 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Local 112 (Springfield, MA) includes ARMA arbitration, 1947-1961 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Local 114 (Camden, AR), 1945 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Local 119 (Providence, RI), 1948-1958, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Local 121 (Hawaii) against veteran-hiring preference, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Local 123 (Denver, CO), 1949-1958 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Local 131 (Grand Rapids, MI), 1952 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Local 133 (Newark, NJ) includes cityworkers' increases, 1946-1961 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Local 133 (Newark, NJ) includes cityworkers' increases, 1946-1961 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Local 138 (Northeast PA), 1951 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Local 139 (Los Angeles, CA), 1951 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Local 140 (Pittsfield, MA), 1954-1962 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Local 142 (Lynn, MA), 1952-1965 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Local 143 (Chicago, IL) reorganized local and its rivals, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Local 149 (Lynn, MA), 1952-1963, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Local 151 (Quincy, MA) includes Bethlehem Steel Strike, 1952, 1960-1962 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Local 152 (Philadelphia) (See also 11/Aetna 1955), 1952-1960 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Local 154 (Philadelphia), 1952, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Local 161 (Elmira, NY), 1953, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Local 162 (Brooklyn, NY) on legislation, 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Local 164 (Peterboro, Ontario) includes strike, 1955, 1964, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Local 167 (Kankakee, IL) includes agreement, 1953-1961, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Local 174 (Long Beach, CA), 1962 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Local 182 (Hartford, CN), 1958 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Local 191 (NYC), 1964 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Local 192 (Storrs, CN)- Miles Holmes re carpenters' raid, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Local 194 (NJ Turnpike Employees) circular, newspaper, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Local 195 (Haddonfield, NJ - highway engineers), 1961 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Local 199 (Maine) suspension, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Local 202 (Bradford, MA), 1952-1954 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Local 209 (Camden, NJ), 1960-1964 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Local 211 (Pottsfield, PA), 1965 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Local 213 (Pottsfield, PA), 1961, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Local 21G (Fairlawn, VA) fundraising for negotiating committee, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Local 241 (Camden, NJ) includes newsletters and bulletins, 1951-1967 (Box 9, Folder 67)
- Series III: Other Unions and Organizations, 1936-1978, 3
  - Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians CIO: Correspondence re: joint activities, WPA workers and prevailing wages; conference notes, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians CIO: Correspondence on cross accusations, joint work, 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians CIO: Correspondence, 1939-1947 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians CIO: "Communist control" - Rep. Dies' report and correspondence (copies from Walter E. Johnson, former FAECT v.p.), 1938-1941 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians CIO: "Communist activities" - newsclippings, CR reprint, 1936-1947 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians CIO: NLRB cases on appropriate bargaining unit, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians CIO: Circulars from NY local: WPA strike, organizing campaign, 1936-1938 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians CIO: Circulars and publications: organizing, war production, Ebasco strike, 1939-1949 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Non-Union Associations of Engineers and Management: American Academy of Professional Draftsmen (membership), 1959 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Non-Union Associations of Engineers and Management: American Society of Mechanical Engineers, Junior Group, NYC: discussion notes on "should engineers unionize", 1947, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Non-Union Associations of Engineers and Management: American Society of Mechanical Engineers and Am. Soc. of Civil Engineers: circular, article, and newsletter, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Non-Union Associations of Engineers and Management: Council for the Advancement of the Negro in Architecture: newsletter and statement of aims, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Non-Union Associations of Engineers and Management: Engineers Joint Council: Engineer journal and guidelines, 1969, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Non-Union Associations of Engineers and Management: National Society of Professional Engineers: "dipping toes in union surf", articles, circulars, 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Non-Union Associations of Engineers and Management: Management groups: antiunion materials, early 1960s (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Non-Union Associations of Engineers and Management: Tool Owners Union, profit-sharing association, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): AFL and AFL-CIO, correspondence; DC headquarters dedication, 1952-1957 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): AFL - Labor's League for Political Education (later COPE), 1952-1956 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): AFL - COPE circulars, 1956-1958 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): AFL-CIO: convention call correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): AFL-CIO "6-point program for jobs", 1975 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): AFL-CIO - Long Island Federation of Labor campaign for full employment, 1963-1967 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): AFL-CIO - Rockland County Central Labor...Council meeting, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): AFL offices and regions correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): New York State AFL correspondence, convention resolutions, 1949-1955 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): New York State AFL correspondence, convention resolutions, 1949-1955 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): New York State AFL correspondence, convention resolutions, 1949-1955 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): New York State AFL-CIO conventions, legislative work, 1956-1965 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): New York State AFL-CIO conventions, legislative work, 1956-1965 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): New York State AFL-CIO conventions, legislative work, 1956-1965 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): Brooklyn Board of Business Agents correspondence, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): Bronx Board of Business Agents correspondence, 1949-1960 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): Building and Construction Trades Council correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): Building and Construction Trades Council master agreement, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): Building and Construction Trades Council: Field Engineers and Surveyors strike (withholds secondary pickets), 1950-1951 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): Building and Construction Trades Council re: reaffiliation, 1959-1961 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): Building and Construction Trades Councils (other than NYC), 1950-1956 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): Central Labor Council (strike support, socials, campaigns) 1953-thumbnail sketch of Local 66 history, 1952-1964 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): Industrial Union Department (IUD) conference, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): Industrial Union Department publications, correspondence, 1963, 1964, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): Maritime Port Council of Greater New York constitution, strike support, boycott of Cuban ships (1962), minutes and certificate of affiliation, 1960-1964 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): New York Metal Trades District Council meeting notices, 1963-1966 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Affiliates (AFL Bodies, Councils, Boards): Union Label and Service Trades Department/NY, 1952-1966 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Independent Engineering Unions: General Electric; Western Electric engineers: salaries, 1946-1948 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Independent Engineering Unions: Engineers and Scientists of America constitution, 1948? (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Independent Engineering Unions: Engineers and Architects Association (Los Angeles) bulletin, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of America: "Check that Chick" campaign brochure, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: Association of Catholic Trade Unionists criticizes Local 66 and JLR re: Mergenthaler raid. See also 5/27., 1961 (Box 10, Folder 31a)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: Bartenders Union, Local 15 building fund, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: Bricklayer's Union Locals correspondence (Local 37), 1952-1961 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: Brotherhood Railroad Signalmen of America: NY Central, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: Building Employees Int'l Union, Local 32E souvenir journal, 1955-1963 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: Building, Heavy and Highway Construction Local 754, thanks for strike support, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: Civil Service Technical Guild affiliation with CIO, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: New York State Employees Council (AFSCME) correspondence, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: Hotel and Motel Workers of NY newspaper, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: Insurance Agents' International, Local 19 souvenir journal ("they can help spread our (union) gospel," writes JLR), 1954 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: International Association of Machinists locals, strike support; Foster Wheeler strike, 1953-1956, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers strike support and member referral, 1952-1960 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Other Unions and Labor Associations: Iron Workers Shopmen's Local 455 strike support and souvenir journals, 1950-1961, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 43)